Dennis DeConcini Papers 1944-2008
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Subgroup 3: Congressional Activities. 1944-1998
  - Series 2: Legislative Committee Files. 1954-1994
    - Subseries 10: Foreign Relations. 1976-1994
      - Saudi Arabia. 1980-1986 (Box 168, Folder 7)
      - Saudi Arabia. 1989-1993 (Box 168, Folder 8)
      - Singapore. 1994 (Box 168, Folder 9)
      - Sino-American Nuclear Verification Act. 1985 (Box 168, Folder 10)
      - Sino-Soviet Summit. 1989 (Box 168, Folder 11)
      - Slepak Principles Act. 1989 (Box 168, Folder 12)
      - Somalia. 1992-1993 (Box 168, Folder 13)
      - South Africa. 1977-1994 (Box 168, Folder 14)
      - South Africa. 1985-1992 (Box 168, Folder 15)
      - South Africa. 1988-1991 (Box 168, Folder 16)
      - South Africa. 1991-1992 (Box 168, Folder 17)
      - South Korea. 1985-1986 (Box 168, Folder 18)
      - South Korea. 1986-1988 (Box 168, Folder 19)
      - South Korea. 1986-1991 (Box 168, Folder 20)
      - Soviet Union. 1979 (Box 168, Folder 21)
      - Soviet Union. 1981-1991 (Box 168, Folder 22)
      - Strategic Arms Limitation Talks (SALT) II. 1977-1979 (Box 168, Folder 23)
      - Strategic Arms Limitation Talks (SALT) II. 1978-1979 (Box 168, Folder 24)
      - Strategic Arms Limitation Talks (SALT) II. 1979 (Box 168, Folder 25-26)
      - Strategic Arms Limitation Talks (SALT) II. 1979-1986 (Box 169, Folder 1)
      - Sweden. 1991 (Box 169, Folder 2)
      - Syria. 1986-1994 (Box 169, Folder 3)
      - Taiwan. 1979-1985 (Box 169, Folder 4)
      - Terrorism. 1982-1989 (Box 169, Folder 5)
      - Terrorism. 1991-1993 (Box 169, Folder 6)
      - Test Ban Treaty. 1985-1987 (Box 169, Folder 7)
      - Tiananmen Square Demonstrators, Nobel Prize Nomination. 1989-1990 (Box 169, Folder 8)
      - Tibet. 1989-1993 (Box 169, Folder 9)
      - Torture Convention. 1988-1989 (Box 169, Folder 10)
      - Treaties. 1986 (Box 169, Folder 11)
      - Turkey. 1990-1994 (Box 169, Folder 12)
      - Turkish-Israeli Relations. 1981 (Box 169, Folder 13)
      - United Nations. 1985-1994 (Box 169, Folder 14)
      - United States Information Agency. 1983-1985 (Box 169, Folder 15)
      - United States Institute for Peace. 1984-1987 (Box 169, Folder 16)
      - Vietnam. 1977-1986 (Box 169, Folder 17)
      - Vietnam. 1977-1994 (Box 169, Folder 18)
      - Warnke Nomination. 1977-1979 (Box 169, Folder 19)
      - Yemeni Jews. 1989-1990 (Box 169, Folder 20)
      - Zaire. 1987-1990 (Box 169, Folder 21)
      - Zimbabwe. 1979 (Box 169, Folder 22)
    - Subseries 11: Government Affairs, 1977-1994
      - Accounting and Management. 1978 (Box 169, Folder 23)
      - Administrative Dispute Resolution. 1988-1990 (Box 169, Folder 24)
      - Administrative Dispute Resolution. 1989-1990 (Box 169, Folder 25)
      - American Association of Retired Persons. 1985 (Box 169, Folder 26)
      - American Federation of Government Employees. 1987-1989 (Box 169, Folder 27)
      - Catastrophic Health Insurance. 1987-1988 (Box 169, Folder 28)
      - Census 1990. 1989-1991 (Box 169, Folder 29-30)
      - Census 1990. 1991 (Box 169, Folder 31)
      - Census 1990. 1992-1994 (Box 170, Folder 1)
      - Civil Service, General. 1977-1981 (Box 170, Folder 2)
      - Civil Service Health Benefits. 1978-1985 (Box 170, Folder 3)
      - Civil Service Retirement "Catch 62". 1984-1987 (Box 170, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Technicians in National Guard, Federal Benefits. 1989-1990 (Box 170, Folder 5)
      - Colorado River Floodway. 1983-1986 (Box 170, Folder 6)
      - Competition in Contracting Act. 1988 (Box 170, Folder 7)
      - Computer Crime Prevention Act. 1984-1985 (Box 170, Folder 8)
      - Congressional Financial Disclosure. 1976-1977 (Box 170, Folder 9)
      - Congressional Honoraria Ban. 1988-1993 (Box 170, Folder 10)
      - Congressional Honoraria Receipts. 1988-1990 (Box 170, Folder 11)
      - Congressional Pay Raise. 1985-1988 (Box 170, Folder 12)
      - Congressional Pay Raise. 1987-1990 (Box 170, Folder 13)
      - Congressional Pay Raise. 1988 (Box 170, Folder 14)
      - Congressional Pay Raise. 1989 (Box 170, Folder 15)
      - Congressional Pay Raise. 1989-1990 (Box 170, Folder 16)
      - Contractor Legal Fees. 1988 (Box 170, Folder 17)
      - Contracting Out. 1983-1988 (Box 170, Folder 18)
      - Co-sponsorship of Bills. 1987-1988 (Box 170, Folder 19)
      - Cost of Living Adjustments for Federal Retirees. 1987-1989 (Box 170, Folder 20)
      - Cost Overruns on Federal Projects. 1982-1983 (Box 170, Folder 21)
      - Debt Collection and Delinquency Prevention Advisory Panel. 1983-1987 (Box 170, Folder 22)
      - Department of Agriculture Reorganization. 1990-1994 (Box 170, Folder 23)
      - Department of Education Act. 1976-1979 (Box 170, Folder 24)
      - Department of Energy Reorganization. 1977-1983 (Box 170, Folder 25)
      - Devine Confirmation. 1985 (Box 170, Folder 26)
      - District of Columbia Civil Contempt Incarceration Amendments. 1989 (Box 170, Folder 27)
      - District of Columbia Insurance Law. 1987 (Box 170, Folder 28)
      - District of Columbia Statehood Issues. 1977-1993 (Box 170, Folder 29)
      - Drug Testing. 1987-1988 (Box 170, Folder 30)
      - Early Retirement. 1987 (Box 170, Folder 31)
      - Employment, Poverty and Migratory Labor. 1977-1980 (Box 170, Folder 32)
      - Ethics in Government Reform Act. 1989-1993 (Box 170, Folder 33)
      - Fair Employment in Congress Act. 1988-1989 (Box 170, Folder 34)
      - Federal Acquisition Streamlining Act. 1992-1994 (Box 170, Folder 35)
      - Federal Advisory Committees. 1988-1989 (Box 171, Folder 1)
      - Federal Advisory Committees. 1994 (Box 171, Folder 2)
      - Federal Employees Associations. 1981-1991 (Box 171, Folder 3)
      - Federal Employees Benefits. 1981-1991 (Box 171, Folder 4)
      - Federal Employees Compensation. 1984-1988 (Box 171, Folder 5)
      - Federal Employees' Distrust. 1988 (Box 171, Folder 6)
      - Federal Employees Pay Raises and Benefits. 1987 (Box 171, Folder 7)
      - Federal Employees Retirement. 1983-1988 (Box 171, Folder 8)
      - Federal Employees Retirement System. 1986-1990 (Box 171, Folder 9)
      - Federal Employees Wage Garnishment. 1987-1988 (Box 171, Folder 10)
      - Federal Employees Who Perform Active Military Duty. 1990 (Box 171, Folder 11)
      - Federal Managers Association. 1987-1988 (Box 171, Folder 12)
      - Federal Mandate Accountability and Reform Act. 1994 (Box 171, Folder 13)
      - Federal Salary Act. 1977 (Box 171, Folder 14)
      - Federal Spending Practices. 1978-1980 (Box 171, Folder 15)
      - Firefighters Pay Fairness Act. 1977-1994 (Box 171, Folder 16)
      - Flextime. 1980-1982 (Box 171, Folder 17)
      - Former Presidents Act. 1986-1993 (Box 171, Folder 18)
      - General. 1977-1978 (Box 171, Folder 19)
      - General. 1977-1990 (Box 171, Folder 20)
      - General. 1987-1988 (Box 171, Folder 21)
      - General Services Administration, Federal Telecommunications System. 1987-1988 (Box 171, Folder 22)
      - General Services Administration, Federal Telecommunications System. 1988 (Box 171, Folder 23)
      - Global Resources, Environment, and Population Act. 1987 (Box 171, Folder 24)
      - Hatch Act Reform. 1987-1988 (Box 171, Folder 25-26)
      - Hatch Act Reform. 1987-1989 (Box 171, Folder 27)
      - Hatch Act Reform. 1987-1991 (Box 171, Folder 28)
      - Hatch Act Reform. 1989-1994 (Box 171, Folder 29)
      - Hatch Act Reform. 1989 (Box 171, Folder 30)
      - Healthcare Freedom of Choice Act. 1987 (Box 171, Folder 31)
      - Health Maintenance Organizations. 1978-1979 (Box 171, Folder 32)
      - Hispanic Affairs. 1977-1993 (Box 172, Folder 1)
      - Hispanic Affairs. 1979-1988 (Box 172, Folder 2)
      - Hollings Amendment Trade Bill. 1987 (Box 172, Folder 3)
      - Inspector General Act. 1987-1988 (Box 172, Folder 4)
      - Intergovernmental Relations. 1977-1980 (Box 172, Folder 5)
      - Investment Policy Act. 1977 (Box 172, Folder 6)
      - Japanese-American Internment Reparations. 1980-1988 (Box 172, Folder 7)
      - Japanese-American Internment Reparations, Civil Liberties Act. 1992 (Box 172, Folder 8)
      - Joint Committee on the Reorganization of Congress. 1993 (Box 172, Folder 9)
      - Joint Committee on the Reorganization of Congress. 1993-1994 (Box 172, Folder 10)
      - Leavesharing. 1988 (Box 172, Folder 11)
      - Lobbyist Disclosure Act. 1991-1994 (Box 172, Folder 12)
      - Long-term Care Insurance. 1987-1991 (Box 172, Folder 13)
      - Lotteries. 1981-1985 (Box 172, Folder 14)
      - Luke Air Force Base-Civilian Workers Union. 1987-1988 (Box 172, Folder 15)
      - Memoranda. 1985 (Box 172, Folder 16)
      - Merit Systems Protection Board. 1986-1988 (Box 172, Folder 17)
      - Minority Business Development. 1977-1978 (Box 172, Folder 18)
      - National Association of Retired Federal Employees. 1985-1989 (Box 172, Folder 19)
      - National Performance Review. 1992-1993 (Box 172, Folder 20)
      - National Service Opportunities Act. 1985-1986 (Box 172, Folder 21)
      - National Treasury Employees Union. 1986-1989 (Box 172, Folder 22)
      - Negotiated Rulemaking Act. 1986-1989 (Box 172, Folder 23)
      - Nuclear Non-proliferation. 1977-1989 (Box 172, Folder 24)
      - Office of Personnel Management. 1987-1990 (Box 172, Folder 25)
      - Oversight of Government Management. 1993 (Box 172, Folder 26)
      - Pay Equity. 1985-1987 (Box 172, Folder 27)
      - Pay Equity. 1987-1988 (Box 173, Folder 1)
      - Pay Reform. 1981-1988 (Box 173, Folder 2)
      - Peace Corps Drug Scandal. 1984-1987 (Box 173, Folder 3)
      - Perk Legislation. 1993 (Box 173, Folder 4)
      - Postal Employees Appeal Rights. 1987-1989 (Box 173, Folder 5)
      - Postal Employees Budget Agreement. 1990 (Box 173, Folder 6)
      - Program Evaluation Act. 1977-1978 (Box 173, Folder 7)
      - Prompt Payment Act. 1985-1987 (Box 173, Folder 8)
      - Prompt Payment Act. 1988 (Box 173, Folder 9)
      - Prompt Payment Act. 1988-1989 (Box 173, Folder 10)
      - Public Officials Integrity Act. 1977 (Box 173, Folder 11)
      - Reagan Land-Sale Plan. 1981-1982 (Box 173, Folder 12)
      - Regulatory Reform Act. 1977 (Box 173, Folder 13)
      - Regulatory Review Sunshine Act. 1991-1992 (Box 173, Folder 14)
      - Responsible Government Act. 1992-1993 (Box 173, Folder 15)
      - Secrecy Oath Bar. 1987-1988 (Box 173, Folder 16)
      - Seniority System. 1987 (Box 173, Folder 17)
      - Social Security. 1985 (Box 173, Folder 18)
      - Smoking Restrictions in Federal Buildings. 1986-1987 (Box 173, Folder 19)
      - Sunset Act. 1977-1979 (Box 173, Folder 20)
      - Unfunded Federal Mandates. 1993-1994 (Box 173, Folder 21)
      - Voter Registration. 1981-1985 (Box 173, Folder 22)
      - Washington Metro Compact. 1990 (Box 173, Folder 23)
      - Water Resources. 1984-1985 (Box 173, Folder 24-25)
      - Waterfront Corruption. 1981 (Box 173, Folder 26)
      - Whistleblower Protection Act. 1986-1989 (Box 173, Folder 27)
    - Subseries 12: Helsinki, 1975-1994
      - Activities. 1985-1989 (Box 173, Folder 28)
      - Afghanistan. 1985-1990 (Box 174, Folder 1)
      - Africa. 1991 (Box 174, Folder 2)
      - Albania, Bulgaria, Czechoslovakia, and Berlin. 1990 (Box 174, Folder 3)
      - Association of Soviet Lawyers. 1982-1985 (Box 174, Folder 4)
      - Association of Soviet Lawyers. 1986 (Box 174, Folder 5)
      - Association of Soviet Lawyers. 1987-1988 (Box 174, Folder 6)
      - Amnesty International. 1987 (Box 174, Folder 7)
      - Annual Reports. 1984-1987 (Box 174, Folder 8)
      - Armenia. 1984-1988 (Box 174, Folder 9)
      - Armenia, Azerbaijan and Central Asia. 1991-1992 (Box 174, Folder 10)
      - Armenia, Azerbaijan and Central Asia. 1992 (Box 174, Folder 11-12)
      - Arms Control. 1989-1991 (Box 174, Folder 13)
      - Baltic States. 1987-1991 (Box 174, Folder 14)
      - Baltic States. 1989 (Box 174, Folder 15)
      - Baltic States. 1992-1993 (Box 174, Folder 16)
      - Bern Experts Meeting on Human Contacts. 1986 (Box 174, Folder 17)
      - Bosnia. 1990-1992 (Box 174, Folder 18)
      - Bosnia. 1992-1994 (Box 174, Folder 19-20)
      - Bosnia. 1993 (Box 174, Folder 21-22)
      - Briefing Book. 1986 (Box 175, Folder 1)
      - Budapest. 1994 (Box 175, Folder 2)
      - Budapest and Cultural Forum. 1985 (Box 175, Folder 3)
      - Budget. 1987-1988 (Box 175, Folder 4)
      - Bulgaria. 1987-1989 (Box 175, Folder 5)
      - A Changing Soviet Society Hearing. 1989 (Box 175, Folder 6)
      - Charter of Paris for a New Europe. 1990 (Box 175, Folder 7)
      - China. 1985-1986 (Box 175, Folder 8)
      - Colloquy on United States Delegations. 1991 (Box 175, Folder 9)
      - Commission on Security and Cooperation in Europe. 1983-1985 (Box 175, Folder 10)
      - Commission on Security and Cooperation in Europe Digest. 1985-1986 (Box 175, Folder 11)
      - Congressional Actions. 1984-1992 (Box 175, Folder 12)
      - Congressional Delegation to Soviet Union and Denmark. 1987-1988 (Box 175, Folder 13)
      - Congressional Delegation to Soviet Union and Denmark. 1987-1989 (Box 175, Folder 14)
      - Congressional Delegation to Soviet Union and Denmark. 1988 (Box 175, Folder 15-18)
      - Congressional Delegation to Soviet Union and Denmark. 1988-1989 (Box 175, Folder 19)
      - Congressional Record. 1987-1991 (Box 175, Folder 20)
      - Copenhagen Meeting. 1990 (Box 175, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence, General. 1986-1990 (Box 175, Folder 22)
      - Correspondence, Human Rights. 1986-1987 (Box 175, Folder 23)
      - Correspondence, Personal (Regarding Retirement). 1994 (Box 175, Folder 24)
      - Czechoslovakia. 1987-1989 (Box 175, Folder 25)
      - Divided Spouses Coalition. 1985-1987 (Box 175, Folder 26)
      - Eastern Europe. 1989-1992 (Box 175, Folder 27)
      - Eastern Europe Perestroika Hearing. 1988 (Box 176, Folder 1)
      - Eastern Europe Policies on Emigration. 1986 (Box 176, Folder 2)
      - Eastern Europe and the Soviet Union. 1987 (Box 176, Folder 3)
      - East-West Trade and the Helsinki Process. 1990 (Box 176, Folder 4)
      - Egypt. 1993 (Box 176, Folder 5)
      - Estonia. 1992 (Box 176, Folder 6)
      - Europe, Codels DeConcini. 1983-1992 (Box 176, Folder 7)
      - Family Visitation with Soviet Relatives. 1986-1988 (Box 176, Folder 8)
      - Foreign Affairs. 1991 (Box 176, Folder 9)
      - Freedom Support Act. 1991-1993 (Box 176, Folder 10)
      - General. 1985-1991 (Box 176, Folder 11)
      - General. 1985-1993 (Box 176, Folder 12)
      - General. 1987-1989 (Box 176, Folder 13)
      - General. 1987-1990 (Box 176, Folder 14)
      - General. 1988 (Box 176, Folder 15)
      - General. 1988-1989 (Box 176, Folder 16)
      - General. 1989-1990 (Box 176, Folder 17)
      - General. 1992 (Box 176, Folder 18)
      - Genocide Convention. 1985-1986 (Box 176, Folder 19)
      - German Reunification. 1990 (Box 176, Folder 20)
      - Glasnost. 1987 (Box 176, Folder 21)
      - Greece. 1986-1994 (Box 176, Folder 22)
      - Helsinki Accords. 1980-1992 (Box 176, Folder 23)
      - Holocaust Days of Remembrance Ceremony. 1987 (Box 176, Folder 24)
      - Human Rights. 1985 (Box 176, Folder 25)
      - Human Rights. 1985-1986 (Box 177, Folder 1)
      - Human Rights. 1985-1993 (Box 177, Folder 2)
      - Human Rights. 1988 (Box 177, Folder 3)
      - Human Rights Day. 1975-1985 (Box 177, Folder 4)
      - Human Rights Day. 1986-1989 (Box 177, Folder 5)
      - Human Rights Day. 1990-1994 (Box 177, Folder 6)
      - Hungary. 1981-1988 (Box 177, Folder 7)
      - Hungary, Greece, Macedonia and Croatia. 1992 (Box 177, Folder 8-9)
      - Selma Hurwitz Art Exhibit. 1989 (Box 177, Folder 10)
      - Intermediate-Range Nuclear Forces Treaty. 1978-1987 (Box 177, Folder 11)
      - Intermediate-Range Nuclear Forces Treaty. 1987-1988 (Box 177, Folder 12)
      - Intermediate-Range Nuclear Forces Treaty. 1988-1992 (Box 177, Folder 13)
      - Ireland. 1992 (Box 177, Folder 14)
      - Jackson-Vanik Trade Restrictions. 1974-1988 (Box 177, Folder 15)
      - Jackson-Vanik Trade Restrictions. 1989 (Box 177, Folder 16-17)
      - Jackson-Vanik Trade Restrictions. 1990-1991 (Box 177, Folder 18)
      - Jewish Heritage Week. 1987-1988 (Box 177, Folder 19)
      - Kenya, Somalia, Cyprus, Romania and Kosovo. 1993 (Box 177, Folder 20)
      - Latvia. 1989-1990 (Box 177, Folder 21)
      - Lithuania. 1987-1992 (Box 177, Folder 22)
      - Madrid and Copenhagen. 1983 (Box 178, Folder 1)
      - McCarren-Walter Act. 1979-1986 (Box 178, Folder 2)
      - McClure Amendment. 1974-1988 (Box 178, Folder 3)
      - Medvid Hearings. 1987 (Box 178, Folder 4)
      - Mediterranean. 1990 (Box 178, Folder 5)
      - Meetings. 1978-1987 (Box 178, Folder 6)
      - Mexico. 1986-1987 (Box 178, Folder 7)
      - Middle East. 1988-1989 (Box 178, Folder 8)
      - Monitoring Groups in the U.S.S.R. and Lithuania. 1986 (Box 178, Folder 9)
      - Morocco. 1987 (Box 178, Folder 10)
      - Nationalities Issue in the Soviet Union. 1988 (Box 178, Folder 11)
      - News Releases. 1985 (Box 178, Folder 12)
      - Nobel Peace Prize. 1973-1989 (Box 178, Folder 13)
      - Ottawa Human Rights Experts Meeting. 1984-1985 (Box 178, Folder 14)
      - Ottawa Human Rights Experts Meeting. 1985 (Box 178, Folder 15-17)
      - Palestine Liberation Organization. 1986-1989 (Box 178, Folder 18)
      - Paris Conference on Security and Cooperation in Europe. 1989 (Box 178, Folder 19-21)
      - Poland. 1987-1993 (Box 178, Folder 22)
      - Pollution in the Soviet Union and Eastern Europe. 1988 (Box 178, Folder 23)
      - Psychiatric Abuse. 1989 (Box 178, Folder 24)
      - Refuseniks-Abramovich, Pavel. no date (Box 178, Folder 25)
      - Refuseniks-Alpert, Jacov. 1979-1987 (Box 178, Folder 26)
      - Refuseniks-Begun, Iosef. 1982-1987 (Box 178, Folder 27)
      - Refuseniks-Beracha, Reuben and Lidia. 1983-1984 (Box 179, Folder 1)
      - Refuseniks-Berenshtein, Iosif and Yana. 1985-1986 (Box 179, Folder 2)
      - Refuseniks-Blitshtein, Lev. 1979-1987 (Box 179, Folder 3)
      - Refuseniks-Bogomolny, Veniamin and Tatiana. 1985-1986 (Box 179, Folder 4)
      - Refuseniks-Brailovsky, Viktor. 1980-1983 (Box 179, Folder 5)
      - Refuseniks-Braun, Keith and Svetlana. 1985-1992 (Box 179, Folder 6)
      - Refuseniks-Brodsky, Vladimir. 1985-1986 (Box 179, Folder 7)
      - Refuseniks-Bukham, Mikhail. 1988 (Box 179, Folder 8)
      - Refuseniks-Cancer Patients. 1986-1987 (Box 179, Folder 9)
      - Refuseniks-Chernyak, Yuri. 1985-1992 (Box 179, Folder 10)
      - Refuseniks-Christian Dissidents. 1979-1983 (Box 179, Folder 11)
      - Refuseniks-Correspondence (Outgoing). 1986 (Box 179, Folder 12)
      - Refuseniks-Dashevsky, Vladimir. 1988 (Box 179, Folder 13)
      - Refuseniks-Donetsk Death Sentences. 1980 (Box 179, Folder 14)
      - Refuseniks-Dubianskaya, Elena. 1985 (Box 179, Folder 15)
      - Refuseniks-Elbert, Lev. 1983-1987 (Box 179, Folder 16)
      - Refuseniks-Essas, Ilya. 1986 (Box 179, Folder 17)
      - Refuseniks-Federov, Valery and Svayonia. 1987 (Box 179, Folder 18)
      - Refuseniks-Federov, Yuri. 1979-1980 (Box 179, Folder 19)
      - Refuseniks-Feldman, Vladimir and Efim. 1986-1987 (Box 179, Folder 20)
      - Refuseniks-Finkelstein, Eitan and Alexandra. 1981-1984 (Box 179, Folder 21)
      - Refuseniks-Fradkin, Daniel and Sarah. 1983-1985 (Box 179, Folder 22)
      - Refuseniks-Freidlin, Mark. 1984-1986 (Box 179, Folder 23)
      - Refuseniks-Friedman, Paul. 1990 (Box 179, Folder 24)
      - Refuseniks-Foster, Liliana. 1983-1988 (Box 179, Folder 25)
      - Refuseniks-Fulmakht, Viktor. no date (Box 179, Folder 26)
      - Refuseniks-Gajauskas, Balys. 1985 (Box 179, Folder 27)
      - Refuseniks-Gendin, Lev. 1976-1978 (Box 179, Folder 28)
      - Refuseniks-General. 1977-1978 (Box 179, Folder 29)
      - Refuseniks-General. 1977-1992 (Box 179, Folder 30)
      - Refuseniks-General. 1978 (Box 179, Folder 31)
      - Refuseniks-General. 1978-1980 (Box 179, Folder 32)
      - Refuseniks-General. 1978-1984 (Box 179, Folder 33)
      - Refuseniks-General. 1978-1985 (Box 179, Folder 34)
      - Refuseniks-General. 1978-1987 (Box 179, Folder 35)
      - Refuseniks-General. 1979-1985 (Box 179, Folder 36)
      - Refuseniks-General. 1979-1987 (Box 179, Folder 37)
      - Refuseniks-General. 1983-1992 (Box 179, Folder 38)
      - Refuseniks-General. 1985-1990 (Box 179, Folder 39)
      - Refuseniks-General. 1986-1988 (Box 179, Folder 40)
      - Refuseniks-General. 1987 (Box 180, Folder 1)
      - Refuseniks-General. 1988 (Box 180, Folder 2)
      - Refuseniks-General. 1988-1993 (Box 180, Folder 3)
      - Refuseniks-General. 1989-1990 (Box 180, Folder 4)
      - Refuseniks-Genusov, Gregory and Helena. 1981 (Box 180, Folder 5)
      - Refuseniks-Ghica, Ulpia. 1986-1989 (Box 180, Folder 6)
      - Refuseniks-Goldfard, Boris and Elena. 1985-1987 (Box 180, Folder 7)
      - Refuseniks-Goldshtein, Grigory and Isay. 1974-1986 (Box 180, Folder 8)
      - Refuseniks-Golenko, Dmituj. 1985 (Box 180, Folder 9)
      - Refuseniks-Gudava Brothers. 1987 (Box 180, Folder 10)
      - Refuseniks-Grauer, Mark. 1987-1988 (Box 180, Folder 11)
      - Refuseniks-Greenblatt, Eugenia. 1980-1987 (Box 180, Folder 12)
      - Refuseniks-Greenfarb, Mendel and Seraya. 1982 (Box 180, Folder 13)
      - Refuseniks-Grinberg, Karl. 1979 (Box 180, Folder 14)
      - Refuseniks-Grivnina, Irina. 1983-1985 (Box 180, Folder 15)
      - Refuseniks-Hess, Grigory and Elena. 1979-1983 (Box 180, Folder 16)
      - Refuseniks-Ioffe, Alexander and Rosa. 1979-1988 (Box 180, Folder 17)
      - Refuseniks-Ioffes and Yakirs. 1986 (Box 180, Folder 18)
      - Refuseniks-Jewish Federation. 1990 (Box 180, Folder 19)
      - Refuseniks-Kalendarov, Boris. 1979-1987 (Box 180, Folder 20)
      - Refuseniks-Kazanevich, Mikhail and Natasha. 1988 (Box 180, Folder 21)
      - Refuseniks-Khachaturyan, Armen and Svetlana. 1985 (Box 180, Folder 22)
      - Refuseniks-Khanukaev, Zahkaria. 1987 (Box 180, Folder 23)
      - Refuseniks-Khassin, Gennady and Natasha. 1984-1987 (Box 180, Folder 24)
      - Refuseniks-Kislik, Vladimir. 1977-1984 (Box 180, Folder 25)
      - Refuseniks-Klotz, Boris. 1984-1987 (Box 180, Folder 26)
      - Refuseniks-Kogan, Izaak and Sofia. 1979-1982 (Box 180, Folder 27)
      - Refuseniks-Koryagin, Anatoly. 1987 (Box 180, Folder 28)
      - Refuseniks-Kosharovsky, Yuli. 1984-1988 (Box 180, Folder 29)
      - Refuseniks-Kotlyar, Mark. 1989-1990 (Box 180, Folder 30)
      - Refuseniks-Lein, Eugeny and Irina. 1982-1989 (Box 180, Folder 31)
      - Refuseniks-Leonov, Arkady and Svetlana. 1984 (Box 180, Folder 32)
      - Refuseniks-Lerner, Alexander and Judith. 1978-1987 (Box 180, Folder 33)
      - Refuseniks-Livshits, Boris and Yalina. no date (Box 180, Folder 34)
      - Refuseniks-Lodisev, Aleski. 1983-1985 (Box 180, Folder 35)
      - Refuseniks-Lurie, Emmanuel and Yudith. 1986-1989 (Box 180, Folder 36)
      - Refuseniks-Mai, Arkady and Elena. 1979-1987 (Box 180, Folder 37)
      - Refuseniks-Magarik, Alexei. 1986-1987 (Box 180, Folder 38)
      - Refuseniks-Marchenko, Anatoly. 1986 (Box 180, Folder 39)
      - Refuseniks-Maryasin, Alexander and Lea. 1978-1986 (Box 180, Folder 40)
      - Refuseniks-Medvid Investigation. 1985-1987 (Box 180, Folder 41)
      - Refuseniks-Meiman, Naum. 1977-1989 (Box 180, Folder 42)
      - Refuseniks-Mendelevich, Iosif. 1979-1981 (Box 180, Folder 43)
      - Refuseniks-Monitoring Groups. 1985 (Box 180, Folder 44)
      - Refuseniks-Murzhenko, Aleksei. 1978-1986 (Box 180, Folder 45)
      - Refuseniks-Niklus, Mart. 1984 (Box 180, Folder 46)
      - Refuseniks-Nudel, Ida. 1979-1986 (Box 180, Folder 47)
      - Refuseniks-Ogurtsov, Igor. 1987 (Box 180, Folder 48)
      - Refuseniks-Ostrovsky, Zinovy. 1987-1988 (Box 180, Folder 49)